<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Thanh Dinh Blog</title>
        <link>https://thanhdinh98.github.io/blog</link>
        <description>Thanh Dinh Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hello World]]></title>
            <link>https://thanhdinh98.github.io/blog/hello-world</link>
            <guid>hello-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[welcome]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img alt="welcome" src="/assets/images/welcome-image-5a3312855bfb5043494531311a68cfd2.jpg" width="4240" height="2832"></p><p><strong>Welcome</strong> to my world! If you haven't known who I am yet, let me take a bit time to introduce a little bit about this little asian boy first.</p><p>My full name is: Đinh Nhật Thanh</p><p>You can</p><ul><li>Call me Thanh when you're my relative, friend or colleague.</li><li>Call me Nhật Thanh if you afraid that someone else in the room would has a same name as me.</li><li>Call me Đinh Nhật Thanh when you feel disapointed on me or really want to get my attention.</li><li>Call me Đinh if you haven't read this article yet, but it's ok.</li></ul><p>Currently, I'm a software developer base in HCMC with a high passion in discovering the tech world.</p><p>I'm writting this very first blog on Feburary 7th - a date after Tet holidy in Vietnam. There would be a lots of things I want to talk in here: not only a welcome message, also the purposes for having this beautiful blog.</p><p>Too long for the introduction? Let's get start!</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_mojV" id="why-do-i-have-this-blog">Why do I have this Blog?<a class="hash-link" href="#why-do-i-have-this-blog" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h3><p>I've been working for over 2 years as a Software Engineer, there's a lots of things I have learned as well as experiences I've gained during working at my previous companies. </p><p>Time goes away with age. I wonder why I don't have a place to store everything through my life and then look back at them after years to see how growth I am. It would be crazy cool, at least with me.</p><p>Not only to carefully keep my memorable memories in the box, I also would like to share all of the things I'll have learned and taken notes on them to be able get the lasted memorizing.</p><p>Yeah, kill two birds with one stone!</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_mojV" id="why-is-this-blog-written-in-english">Why is this Blog written in English?<a class="hash-link" href="#why-is-this-blog-written-in-english" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h3><p>As I see, English nowadays such like a key for the communication, especially for developing countries with the growth rate in technology industry almost 30% for a year as my country. </p><p>It's something like Harry's wand helping us out of the limit of the opportunities in this "flat world" where people have no gap in languages. I can say that it doesn't just a "need" as past 10 years, it's a "must" for now and the next 10 years then.</p><p>Yeah, obviously, I'm trying my best on learning English, it would help me so much for my growth now and in the future. Having this Blog in fully English would be one of the best way to help me improve this key. </p><p>I'm really excited to look back these words after maybe 2 years later. Woo-hoo!</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_mojV" id="what-things-would-be-posted-on-here">What things would be posted on here?<a class="hash-link" href="#what-things-would-be-posted-on-here" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h3><p>A bit reveal to you guys, I would work as Blockchain Engineer at my next company on this 14th. This would be the most exciting and anticipative thing in this year. I would spent almost my time on doing research and working with blockchain's universe. </p><p>So I will mainly post any subjects relating to blockchain's ecosystem. Hope you guys would not see this something scam 😢</p><p>Besides blockchain's posts, I would do some updates on my pet-projects, as well as products built by me.</p><hr><p><strong>One minute for advertisment</strong></p><p>I'm running a product called <a href="https://www.ownprint.co/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">ownprint.co</a>. This is a middle-man service connecting retailer with manufactory for selling products. We follow the dropship model, so you don't need to keep goods sold in stock when an order's placed. The website has fully detailed information would help you out of any concerns.</p><hr><p>Feels kinda boring huh? I have a good news for you. I also have subjects to be posted, which would be everything arounds me during my experience in works and life. </p><p>Something would be cool, fun and a bit crazy sometimes. And ofcourse, all of them would base on my mood at the moment 😆</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_mojV" id="who-would-be-suitable-for-my-blog">Who would be suitable for my Blog?<a class="hash-link" href="#who-would-be-suitable-for-my-blog" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h3><p>Noone else suitable to this Blog more than its owner right? 😄</p><p>Yeah, me would be the big fan of this, this would be something that I can look back after years to know how far I go.</p><p>But going alone is kinda boring to me. I would like to share the experiences to you guys who feels excited and interested in my journey. And I would need your helps to correct my stupidity mistakes. This reminds me to a quote:</p><blockquote><p>If you want to go fast, go alone. If you want to go far, go together. - <strong>African Proverb</strong></p></blockquote><p>I also have one 😄</p><p><code>At the beginning we could be stragers, time by time, we will become friends, and lasted, we will be part of our life</code> - <strong>Thanh Dinh</strong></p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_mojV" id="conclusion">Conclusion.<a class="hash-link" href="#conclusion" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h3><p>Yeah, Tet is end, the year with full of new things and plans is just getting started. There's nothing more than we can do the things we like and live the life we want.</p><p>I will always be positive and spread this energy to people around me. Wish that this year will be a successful year for you and me.</p><p>Let be concentrating and tell me what you've been doing in this year!</p><p>I think this blog is quite long for a "welcome message" 😄. Happy tiger's year and see you guys in the next blog!</p><p>YOLO!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>welcome</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>